W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Ephemera (personal), 1930 - 1979; F-55-17; 37 cm of textual records; Predominant dates are 1940-1970.
  - Menus, 1960 - 1969; F-55-17-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-23)
  - Menus, 1971; F-55-17-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Royal Visit - Brochure, 1971; F-55-17-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Place Mats, F-55-17-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Posters, 1966 - 1969; F-55-17-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Coronation Day Address, 1953; F-55-17-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Royal Address, 1959; F-55-17-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Memorandum of Cooperation - Unsigned printed agreement, 1972; F-55-17-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Transparency, 1975; F-55-17-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949 - 1970; F-55-17-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Standing Orders - Printed material, 1930 - 1941; F-55-17-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
  - Stationery - Letterhead, envelopes, F-55-17-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-24)
- General correspondence, 1941 - 1952; F-55-18; 75 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence regarding election campaigns, the attempted formation of the Coalition Party, the period after W.A.C. Bennett resigned as an M.L.A. to run as the representative for the federal riding of Yale, May 13, 1948 to June 15, 1949, W.A.C. Bennett's term as an independent Member and the development of the Social Credit League. Included are correspondence with non-constituent residents of B.C., with federal M.P.'s, with non-departmental provincial officers such as the Provincial Secretary, the Lieutenant Governor and the Leader of the Opposition, with federal and provincial Progressive Conservative Party members, and correspondence designated for legislative sessions.
  - General Correspondence - Letters, file note. Letters from: Coalie Campbell, George La Fleche, R.J. Gillis, E.T. Evers, S.R. Yates, Howard Green, G.W. Mather, W.J. Jamieson, Ida Royle, D.M. Duggan, Brian Atkinson, R.R. Walker, 1941; F-55-18-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, note. Letters from: J.W. Wright, J.K. Hodges, R.L. Maitland, Art Brodie, J.A. Paton, F. Drewe Pratt, 1941; F-55-18-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, notes, memorandum. Letters from: H.S. Cleasby, W.F. Kennedy, Y. Bell, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: C.F. Rowsell, Nancy Sutton, R.J. Gillis, Pat Woods, Walter Kirchner, R.G. Hardisty, H.S. Cleasby, Grote Stirling, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, balance sheets. Letters from: D.C. Fillmore, Nancy Sutton, George La Fleche, C.F. Rowsell, R.J. Gillis, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, notices. Letters from: G.F. Amyot, A.M.D. Fairbairn, C.F. Banfield, W.R. Webster, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: F.H. Harrison, C.B. Garland, Eva L. Cleland, W.S. Brown, C.E. Campbell, Nancy Sutton, Leighton E. Tripp, Murray Cotterill, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, music score, resolution, list, file note. Letters from: G.J. Rowland, George S. Pearson, John Rowland, A.E. Jukes, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: E.S.H. Winn, C.J. Oliphant, C.B. Garland, J.C. Hackney, W.F. Kennedy, H.H. Stevens, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: H. Frank Bird, L.I. Bearg, 1942; F-55-18-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Earl M. Bennett, O.M. Redhead, J.K. Hodges, 1943; F-55-18-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: F.B. McLeod, Fred J. Green, John Gowans, Frank S. Cunliffe, E.W. Barton, J.D. McMynn, F. Drewe Pratt, E.C. Weddell, R.J. Gillis, 1943; F-55-18-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Violet H. Wilson, Cecil R. Bull, George La Fleche, Tom Love, R.C. Palmer, S.J. White, W.F. Kennedy, J. Albert Abrahamson, W. MacGillivray, 1943; F-55-18-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Dorothy Spurr, R.J. Skelton, N. Love, Fred M. Garland, George E. White, 1943; F-55-18-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: L. Pitkethley, E.W. Griffith, Ernest E. Winch, Albert Coy, 1943; F-55-18-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speech, list. Letters from: J.A. Paton, Duncan K. Kerr, F. Drewe Pratt, John Bowles, C.A. Hayden, Fred M. Garland, Vida Noble, P. Walker, David Murdoch, 1944; F-55-18-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: William H. Hewlett, M.J. Harvey, R.J. Gillis, C.A. Hayden, 1944; F-55-18-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, agenda, minutes. Letters from: T.W.S. Parsons, J.A. Young, Tilly Jean Rolston, Grote Stirling, R.C. MacDonald, W.S. Russell, E.W. Berry, W.R. Henley, J.T. Gawthrop, C.W.A. Smythe, 1944; F-55-18-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-25)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, pamphlet. Letters from: J.A. Paton, W. MacGillivray, W. Metcalfe, H.G.T. Perry, J.T. Gawthrop, George X. Miller, J.G. Simms, Albert Kerr, Grote Stirling, M.E. Nichols, B.A. McKelvie, J.A. Paton, 1944; F-55-18-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: R.C. MacDonald, W.A. Curran, A. Bryan Williams, Ernest E. Winch, 1944; F-55-18-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: C.A. Hayden, Tilly Jean Rolston, E. Brown, Grote Stirling, Fred J. Green, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Tom Love, John N. Burke, Fred Jablonsky, P.M. Richards, J.T. Gawthrop, Charlotte Lucas, S.M. Patterson, J.K. Hodges, Tom Love, J.D. McMynn, George S. Miller, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: George X. Miller, Fred M. Garland, Mat Hassen, J.T. Gawthrop, John S. Chapman, E.G. Baynes, Fielding Lemmon, P. Walker, William Ramsay, E.G. Baynes, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: R.J. Deachman, Mat Hassen, J.A. Paton, Jack Kennedy, J.A. Barclay, Frank Kappel, C.A. Hayden, A.W. Lundell, William J. Johnson, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: Grote Stirling, E.H. Bennett, H. Boone, H.A. Dennison, Audrey C. Peck, P. Walker, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speeches, announcements, lists, transcript. Letters from: A.C. DesBrisay, Tom Love, Frank Kappel, F.W. Green, Glen E. Braden, Tilly Jean Rolston, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, newspaper clipping. Letters from: C.W.A. Smyth, W.J. Sipprell, Clarence Laverty, Grote Stirling, J. Fitzsimmons, C.E. Findlater, J. Lingen Wood, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speech. Letters from: R.G. Robertson, Vyvyan H. Stephens, F. Hurley, George Watson, J.A. Brice, J.H. Ellis, Edna E. Mortimore, 1945; F-55-18-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, newspaper clippings, resolution, list, map. Letters from: W.J. Johnson, R. Graff, F.D. Pratt, J.K. Hodges, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters (carbon copies), speech, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, resolution, newspaper clipping. Letters from: George C. Hume, J.A. Noyes, Alberta M. McGovern, J. Stanley Pearson, C.G. Beeston, Eva S. Cleland, W.A. Carrothers, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-26)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: W.S. Palmer, H.E. Lethebe, Howard Green, John White, R.G. Fawcett, Fred M. Garland, H.G.T. Perry, Hugh Dalton, S. Maurice Carter, Tom Love, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: H.J. Welch, Fred M. Garland, Frank Davey, Tilly Jean Rolston, T.A.H. Taylor, Milo M. Case, C.F. Banfield, R.V. Stuart, George X. Miller, H.G.T. Perry, Robert D. Harvey, Roy G. Phipps, Arthur G. Cameron, M. Caddie Donaldson, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Isaac Patton, Fred M. Garland, R.W. Alward, R.J. McDougall, Roy G. Phipps, J.E. Fry, Fred M. Garland, Tom Love, Everard Clarke, H.M. Leach, W.J. Johnson, C.W. Morrow, Lawrence J. Burpee, 1946; F-55-18-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speech, statement. Letters from: Fred M. Garland, G. Weatherly, Frederick H. Fullerton, W.S. Palmer, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Thomas Dufferin Pattullo, F.D. Pratt, A.R.R. Craig, George S. Pearson, G.L. Buckman, R.G. Wilson, Robert F.G. Green, Clarence Sorensen, Garfield A. King, Margaret Harvey, Colin MacKenzie, Robert D. Harvey, H.G.T. Perry, George X. Miller, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, printed material. Letters from: H.F. Chapin, N.W. Bennett, G.G. McGeer, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech, notes. Letters from: Alex C. Hope, J.G. Simms, S.L. Brice, Jean Bugg, T.M. Gibson, George X. Miller, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech, notes. Letters from: Herbert Anscomb, George X. Miller, Grote Stirling, C.V.F. Barker, C.W. Morrow, William T. Panton, Charles M. Defieux, Tom Love, J. Edwin Eades, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, lists, telegrams, printed material. Letters from: Grote Stirling, H. Gowdridge, C.V. Charters, C.H. Jackson, Merrill Muttart, C.V.F. Barker, Hilda Hesson, Julian H. Ferguson, Robert Wallace, 1947; F-55-18-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Ella J. Harrison, Herbert Anscomb, Ernest W. Fairless, J. Davis, David Howrie, J.L. Jenkins, J.E. Jamieson, C.V.F. Barker, Archer Davis, W. Czarnesky, F.D. Pratt, H.T. Smith, George R. Pearkes, Fred Garland, C.V. Prosser, E.M. Sutherland, 1948; F-55-18-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 55-27)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Eric S. Frost, Robert D. Harvey, R.A. Bell, George Kingsley, J.G.W. Wylie, E.L. Harrison, W.J. Wagstaff, A. Carolyn Bayfield, L. Topliss, H.H. Hesketh, William A.S. Ashworth, George Kingsley, E.M. Hoyt, Henry Mager, 1948; F-55-18-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, lists, printed material. Letters from: R.S. Stuart Yates, E. Davie Fulton, W. Metcalfe, R.A. Pennington, L.W. Williamson, A.L. Burrows, May Kenyon, C.C.I. Merritt, George R. Pearkes, J.B.M. Clarke, John Diefenbaker, John Bracken, Frank Barker, 1948; F-55-18-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speech. Letters from: Margaret Paynter, Annie Hawkey, A.E. Sage, L. Topliss, H.E. Chatham, 1948; F-55-18-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: V.H. Stephens, Arthur H. Cox, A.C. DesBrisay, Russell Underhill, Alec C. Beasley, W. Metcalfe, Fred Garland, H.G.T. Perry, C.E. Sladen, H.V. Acland, 1949; F-55-18-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, cartoon (mimeographed). Letters from: Robert D. Harvey, A. Reg. MacDougall, T. McMahon, R.D. Baker, G.N. Gardner, 1949; F-55-18-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speeches, invoices. Letters from: Howard Green, A.H. Sager, R.W. Mayhew, J.A. Carlson, A.L. Carruthers, Herbert Anscomb, M.H. Burns, C.W. Morrow, 1949; F-55-18-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invoice. Letters from: J.G. Simms, W.R. Webster, J.K. Hodges, Herbert Anscomb, C.V.F. Barker, C.A. Hayden, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence. - Letters, telegrams, speech, pamphlet. Letters from: A. MacNamara, Everard Clarke, J.A. Jones, Les Bewley, T.R.B. Adams, L.O. Johannson, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, notes, telegram. Letters from: F.H. Fullerton, J.A. Wright, John White, W.J. Asselstine, J.A.J. Illington, Les Bewley, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 55-28)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: Grote Stirling, C.A. Hayden, Linley Crease, Edmond Jorre de St. Jorre, Mary C. Cutler, P.D. O'Brian, John Vickers, Marion N. Sherman, Harry D. Harrison, Hubert Hill, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speeches, statement, telegram, agenda. Letters from: H.G. Andrew, C. John Coleridge, C.V.F. Barker, Robert W. Bonner, C.W. Morrow, J.H. Boothe, J.E. Fry, Tom Love, W.F. Myring, D. McCallum, J.E. Fry, H.T. Goodland, H.R. Hatfield, William T. Straith, C.A. Hayden, Gavin C. Mouat, Ralph J. Robinson, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: E. Davie Fulton, Frank Davey, J.G. Cunningham, Hilton Yeung, Tom Love, E.V. Finland, C.V.F. Barker, Robert W. Bonner, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, speeches (including handwritten speech), telegram, printed material. Letters from: C.J. Copithorne, W. Hardy, C.V.F. Barker, J. Madeleine Clay, A.G.E. Robbins, Richard Hilker, Isabel Warner, 1950; F-55-18-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: D.M. MacKenzie, Anthony T. Kobayashi, Herbert Anscomb, K.B. Currie, Charles E.S. Walls, Leonard A. Hayman, Peter Dewdney, Herbert Anscomb, Daisy Dawe, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, resolutions, list. Letters from: George Drew, Edith Ritchie, Charles E.S. Walls, Lawrence S. Eckardt, Stuart Chambers, George I. Warren, C.G. Beeston, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Notes. Notes signed: Dr. F.E. Dorchester, Walter [Hendricks?], J.J. Gillis, Charles [Morrow?], E.K. DeBeck, Les Fox, Arthur [Ash?], Bert Cannings, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, invoices, motion paper. Letters from: A.H. Yates, Les Bewley, Anne Curts, George R. Matthews, John White, W.L. Pearson, David McKee, E.K. DeBeck, Frank Bird, Herbert Gargrave, D.S. McDiarmid, Harry Duker, C.J. Frederickson, J.E. Fry, Yendor Notna, Dorothy E. Craig, M.C. Cowie, J. Jaggard, Gavin C. Mouat, Robert Reynolds, C.V. Milton, V. Whalen, Mary Partridge, Nancy Hodges, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speeches, motion papers. Letters from: Gilbert D. Kennedy, John P. Clement, W.J. Barrett-Lennard, H.H. Johnstone, J. Jaggard, E.W. Abraham, H.H. Smith, W.A. Rhodes, A.K. Hemstreet, Patrick Hanley, Hilton Yeung, Alice Cressall, W.F. Cressall, E.T. Evers, R.B. McInnis, Charles N. Pretty, Lyle Wicks, Claire P. Sandey, James W. Wardrop, Clarence Wallace, Gladys Bray, J.V. Mills, D.L. Dumont, Frank E. Dorchester, Edith Birnie, A.H. Lewis, J.C. Connick, D. Krenzler, Robert J. Smith, A.A. Mallory, John V. Acland, Irene Landauer, Harry A. Cox, E.J. Alton, Victor B. Harrison, F.J. Glover, J.G. Maher, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, invoice. Letters from: Gerald Harries, T.S. Boyle, Charles Walker, J.L. Finnerty, Cecil S. Crosby, J.G. Cromack, H.E. Cox, Tilly Jean Rolston, M.D. McKichan, John B.B. Shaw, W.D. Cox, F.L. Skinner, J. Surtees, Archibald Ross, Herbert Fiddes, E.E. Price, Christine M. Fifer, A.G. Schell, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, plan. Letters from: Bonnie Defoe, J.A. Robinson, Lloyd A.J. Hills, Harriet Pelletier, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 55-29)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, list. Letters from: Ronald B. Worley, Hans Klaverwyden, Alf Wurtele, O.R. Baxter, A.G. Dobbyn, E.O. Duke, Lyle Wicks, Gordon Forbes, Aura D. Hudson, Waldo Skillings, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Ronald B. Worley, W.N. Chant, David Saunders, Dorothy M. Salter, Nancy T. O'Flaherty, Stuart Brown, Cyril M. Shelford, J. Vans Macdonald, H.G.T. Perry, 1951; F-55-18-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, file note. Letters from: Ed Inch, Fred H. Stephens, Larry S. Eckardt, Ronald B. Worley, Claude M. Strang, William Manson, Everard Clarke, F.H. Yeomans, Claude D. Powell, Charles W.B. Weeks, T.W. Bridges, D.D. McEachern, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: Howard Green, Gordon B. Bell, Harry Duker, R.W. Comer, D. Mathews, Charles E.S. Walls, W. Wraight, H.H. Darling, Everard Clarke, G. Massey, P.B. LaTrobe, Karl Dybhavn, A.C.W. Gartshore, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: Lawrence S. Eckardt, F.H. Whyte, Dave Young, A.G. Schell, C.H. Pinchback, Lyle Wicks, V. Schjelderup, H.H. Darling, E.S. Jones, Hilda Marshall, R.F. Guppy, Frank J.E. Turner, P.B. Tull, C.F. Ranger, Harry Daniel, Ivan Feltham, D.H. Galbraith, Dudley M. McGeer, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters. Letters from: George E. Buscombe, Lyle Wicks, F.H.M. Codville, J.H. Creighton, A. Duckett, H.H. Darling, Archibald Ross, Hilda Marshall, H.M. Morrison, Eric Yorston, George Hewlett, Don Ellsay, R. Barclay Shaw, Ralph E. Spence, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: Lyle Wicks, Frederick Carveth, Don Watson, Minton Mansell, D.S. Ashdown, Ronald B. Worley, Norman L. Duggan, Dorothy Spurr, Claude D. Powell, Fred H. Stephens, R.F. Gallagher, Menno E. Friesen, Ethel A. Wallace, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: L.H. Shantz, Harry D. Francis, Harry Duker, Archibald Ross, Grace Jolly, Cecil S. Crosby, Ronald B. Worley, S.V.H. Redman, Tom Uphill, Irene Johnston, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams, list. Letters from: J.E. Bennett, E.K. DeBeck, William Falk, Maggie Falk, Lucille Mossman, Clarence Laverty, Ronald B. Worley, F.N. Hales, Percy Mickleburgh, W. Turnbull, Ralph E. Spencer, DMcGugan, Florence Giesty, Roderick Gibbons, David Mouckley, G.N. Gardner, Clarence Wallace, Henry Murton, Tom Uphill, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, Les Bewley,Ronald M. Grant, Tom Love, Arvid Lundell, Stan Carnell, Parker Williams, Ronald B. Worley, DMcPherson, Laura E. Ellis, W.W. McPherson, Harry Duker, M.J. O'Brien, J. Huntly Gordon, Susan K. Orr, Herbert Fiddes, Gerald V. Pelton, S.C. Wilson, A.M. Roberts, R.D.P. Gilday, Trenholme R. Edwards, M. Leo Sweeney, W.N. Kemp, Jack Anderson, W.N. Chant, F. Francis Lovegrove, Rod Mackenzie, Alan Calbert, Owen Dinsdale, Robert A. Flack, W.E. Gordon, J.J. Gillis, K. Fulton, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - General Correspondence - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: C.W. Cox, Eddie Eades, Knox Walkem,G.N. Gardner, R.F. Macnaughton, Ralph J. Rupert,W.G. Todd, Bessie Mulholland Farquharson, William T. Straith, George Cullis, Ira L. Boomer, Vyvyan H. Stephens, E.T. Evers, Cecil Rice-Jones, Carl M. Loeblich, G. Morrin Thompson, Duncan C. MacArthur, Ellen Haglund, Gus Haglund, N.J. Bartman, Jim Nesbitt, D.R. Nicholson, Tom Uphill, 1952; F-55-18-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
  - Notes - Notes, file note, speeches (excerpts), 1942; F-55-18-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
- Election, 1941 - 1945; F-55-19; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of election records. Included are nomination papers and poll statements.
  - Nomination Papers - Nomination papers, poll statements, 1941 - 1945; F-55-19-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-30)
- South Okanagan constituent correspondence, 1941 - 1952; F-55-20; 47 cm of textual records
  Series consists of W.A.C. Bennett's correspondence with constituents in Ellison, Glenmore, Kelowna, Naramata, Okanagan Centre, Okanagan Mission, Peachland, Rutland, Summerland, Trepanier, Westbank and Winfield, correspondence with local Boards of Trade, with the Kelowna Masonic Lodge and with the Okanagan Valley Health Unit. Documented are community issues, the request and concerns of individuals (such as pension and welfare difficulties) and political concerns. There is a gap from May 13, 1948 to June 14, 1949 when W.A.C. Bennett was not the M.L.A. for South Okanagan.
  - Ellison - Letters (carbon copies), 1945; F-55-20-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Glenmore - Letters. Letters from: J.W. Nelson Shepherd, R.W. Corner, Alice E. Tuckey, 1942 - 1952; F-55-20-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters, printed material. Letters from: Pauline Engel, James H. Trenwith, E.W. Barton, F.H. Ingram, E.C. Weddell, Cecil R Bull, Harold A. Truswell, Jennie McDonald, Hugh M. McKenzie, Sam Miller, Felicia Snowsell, J.F Munson, G.T. Jewell, 1941 - 1942; F-55-20-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters. Letters from: Jack Ladd, T.F. McWilliams, E.M Barton, G.H. Dunn, Bill Willcox, Sarah C Homwood, J.M. Hershey, A.K. Loyd, 1942; F-55-20-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters. Letters from: G.H. Dunn, J.M. Hershey, A.K. Loyd, E. Coles, E.S.H. Winn, W. Shugg, 1942; F-55-20-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: T.F. McWilliams, Frank Lucas, W Metcalfe, E.W. Griffith, Dorothy Spurr, Walter F Anderson, Leslie Kerry, William Wilcox, William Hamill, J.F. Munson, J.F. Hampson, P.C. Hiles, J.S. Henderson, W. Meston, 1943; F-55-20-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Frank Dunaway, Stewart Smith, E.W Barton, F.A. Browne, R.G. Rutherford, Frank Lucas, Henry Luckey, Wesley Searle, G.H. Dunn, Joseph Casorso, C.H. Jackson, Margaret Wortman, 1944; F-55-20-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-31)
  - Kelowna - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: H. Waldron, E.M. Barton, J.F Hampson, C.W. Lundy, E.C. Weddell, J.H Creighton, Frank Lucas, G.H. Dunn, Harold A Truswell, Roy B.W. Eden, Dorothy Spurr, A.K Loyd, Derick E. Oliver, E.C. Weddell, C.A Hayden, 1945; F-55-20-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-31)